[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "I think it does matter.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "does", "matter", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 66, "question": "Is that good enough?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "good", "enough", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 67, "answer": "No, it's not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "What Anthony Weiner says, his explanation or the woman standing to his left?", "question_tokens": ["What", "Anthony", "Weiner", "says", ",", "his", "explanation", "or", "the", "woman", "standing", "to", "his", "left", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "Both.", "answer_tokens": ["Both", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anthony Weiner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lanny"]}, "docId": "130723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "RBR", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "How do you know that voters don't say if it's good enough for her, it's good enough for me, on with the politics?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "know", "that", "voters", "do", "n't", "say", "if", "it", "'s", "good", "enough", "for", "her", ",", "it", "'s", "good", "enough", "for", "me", ",", "on", "with", "the", "politics", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "Well, I think Lanny's point earlier was right in the sense that we really don't know for certain how voters are going to react to that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "Lanny", "'s", "point", "earlier", "was", "right", "in", "the", "sense", "that", "we", "really", "do", "n't", "know", "for", "certain", "how", "voters", "are", "going", "to", "react", "to", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bill Clinton"]}, "docId": "130723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "So who should know better about forgiveness?", "question_tokens": ["So", "who", "should", "know", "better", "about", "forgiveness", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "That's exactly what Bill Clinton did.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "exactly", "what", "Bill", "Clinton", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "NN", "WP", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "Was that enough to cover this, or was this new behavior that makes him untrustworthy?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "that", "enough", "to", "cover", "this", ",", "or", "was", "this", "new", "behavior", "that", "makes", "him", "untrustworthy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", ",", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "Well, clearly, he warned us ahead of time and as someone who looks at crisis and tries to mitigate harm, that was wise decision by him.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "clearly", ",", "he", "warned", "us", "ahead", "of", "time", "and", "as", "someone", "who", "looks", "at", "crisis", "and", "tries", "to", "mitigate", "harm", ",", "that", "was", "wise", "decision", "by", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 222, "question": "Why should this matter?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "should", "this", "matter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 223, "answer": "Well, I think this matters because this is no longer a question about a campaign that's really about ideas and issues that they care about.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "this", "matters", "because", "this", "is", "no", "longer", "a", "question", "about", "a", "campaign", "that", "'s", "really", "about", "ideas", "and", "issues", "that", "they", "care", "about", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris"]}, "docId": "130723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "Do you think he had to do that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "he", "had", "to", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "As your crisis manager, I hope you never need my services, my friend, Chris.", "answer_tokens": ["As", "your", "crisis", "manager", ",", "I", "hope", "you", "never", "need", "my", "services", ",", "my", "friend", ",", "Chris", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris"]}, "docId": "130723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "RB", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "What did that moment mean there?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "that", "moment", "mean", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "NN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "You know, Chris, Max and I have been talking about that moment -- obviously, everybody has been talking about that moment quite a bit.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "Chris", ",", "Max", "and", "I", "have", "been", "talking", "about", "that", "moment", "--", "obviously", ",", "everybody", "has", "been", "talking", "about", "that", "moment", "quite", "a", "bit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["William", "Kate"]}, "docId": "130723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "He was there, wasn't he, during the whole labor, stayed overnight?", "question_tokens": ["He", "was", "there", ",", "was", "n't", "he", ",", "during", "the", "whole", "labor", ",", "stayed", "overnight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "We've seen that all along the way with William and Kate.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'ve", "seen", "that", "all", "along", "the", "way", "with", "William", "and", "Kate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris"]}, "docId": "130723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RP", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 383, "question": "Do you think that in their disposition of trying to be normal, trying to be like you, everybody, do you think that may actually magnify the draw to them in this kind of new blush of enthusiasm for the royals?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "in", "their", "disposition", "of", "trying", "to", "be", "normal", ",", "trying", "to", "be", "like", "you", ",", "everybody", ",", "do", "you", "think", "that", "may", "actually", "magnify", "the", "draw", "to", "them", "in", "this", "kind", "of", "new", "blush", "of", "enthusiasm", "for", "the", "royals", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 384, "answer": "I think the jury is out on that, Chris.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "jury", "is", "out", "on", "that", ",", "Chris", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "JJ", ",", "``", "JJ", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 386, "question": "Because a lot of people would say they want them to be loose and mysterious and not normal because they're almost aspirational, I think, right?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "a", "lot", "of", "people", "would", "say", "they", "want", "them", "to", "be", "loose", "and", "mysterious", "and", "not", "normal", "because", "they", "'re", "almost", "aspirational", ",", "I", "think", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 387, "answer": "Yes, but also, you know, I think on some level you're kidding yourself if you can really be, quote-unquote, \"normal.\"", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "but", "also", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "think", "on", "some", "level", "you", "'re", "kidding", "yourself", "if", "you", "can", "really", "be", ",", "quote-unquote", ",", "``", "normal", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "That's really simple, I think, wasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "really", "simple", ",", "I", "think", ",", "was", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Max"], "LOCATION": ["Indiana"]}, "docId": "130723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "Kate, have you figured out how to say that word yet?", "question_tokens": ["Kate", ",", "have", "you", "figured", "out", "how", "to", "say", "that", "word", "yet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RP", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "I like to say it as Max does but it ends coming out with an Indiana accent.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "like", "to", "say", "it", "as", "Max", "does", "but", "it", "ends", "coming", "out", "with", "an", "Indiana", "accent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 454, "question": "This moment as it sets up for what you want in terms of perception but also what you may want personally, how do you think this went?", "question_tokens": ["This", "moment", "as", "it", "sets", "up", "for", "what", "you", "want", "in", "terms", "of", "perception", "but", "also", "what", "you", "may", "want", "personally", ",", "how", "do", "you", "think", "this", "went", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "I think this couldn't have gone any better.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "this", "could", "n't", "have", "gone", "any", "better", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Victoria"]}, "docId": "130723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 487, "question": "I mean, what does that mean historically?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "what", "does", "that", "mean", "historically", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 488, "answer": "Well, historically we haven't seen this since Queen Victoria so it is something very, very new for all of us.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "historically", "we", "have", "n't", "seen", "this", "since", "Queen", "Victoria", "so", "it", "is", "something", "very", ",", "very", "new", "for", "all", "of", "us", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "What did you make of this moment?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "make", "of", "this", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "Well, look, it is incredible just because so many people around the world have been so galvanized by this.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "look", ",", "it", "is", "incredible", "just", "because", "so", "many", "people", "around", "the", "world", "have", "been", "so", "galvanized", "by", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charles", "Charles", "Charles"], "LOCATION": ["Buckingham Palace"]}, "docId": "130723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "CD", "CC", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "RP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "And do you see that now as kind of a carried forward of what he will want for his life as a royal?", "question_tokens": ["And", "do", "you", "see", "that", "now", "as", "kind", "of", "a", "carried", "forward", "of", "what", "he", "will", "want", "for", "his", "life", "as", "a", "royal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "Well, look, she did obviously, and she was the one and she and Prince Charles brought their children up slightly differently from the way Prince Charles had been brought up, whether it was having her children in a hospital, whereas Prince Charles was born in Buckingham Palace, whether it was sending them to a real school rather than homeschooling for a lot of their -- a lot of their young lives, whether it was letting them go out to various theme parks, and other places that were public places.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "look", ",", "she", "did", "obviously", ",", "and", "she", "was", "the", "one", "and", "she", "and", "Prince", "Charles", "brought", "their", "children", "up", "slightly", "differently", "from", "the", "way", "Prince", "Charles", "had", "been", "brought", "up", ",", "whether", "it", "was", "having", "her", "children", "in", "a", "hospital", ",", "whereas", "Prince", "Charles", "was", "born", "in", "Buckingham", "Palace", ",", "whether", "it", "was", "sending", "them", "to", "a", "real", "school", "rather", "than", "homeschooling", "for", "a", "lot", "of", "their", "--", "a", "lot", "of", "their", "young", "lives", ",", "whether", "it", "was", "letting", "them", "go", "out", "to", "various", "theme", "parks", ",", "and", "other", "places", "that", "were", "public", "places", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["William", "Kate"]}, "docId": "130723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 563, "question": "What will it be like for this little boy in terms of how he is treated and when he has to realize who he is?", "question_tokens": ["What", "will", "it", "be", "like", "for", "this", "little", "boy", "in", "terms", "of", "how", "he", "is", "treated", "and", "when", "he", "has", "to", "realize", "who", "he", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "I think it's unfortunate that that's the viewpoint taken already because I think William and Kate have made it very clear that they're going to do everything they can to give their child as loving and well-adjusted childhood as possible.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "unfortunate", "that", "that", "'s", "the", "viewpoint", "taken", "already", "because", "I", "think", "William", "and", "Kate", "have", "made", "it", "very", "clear", "that", "they", "'re", "going", "to", "do", "everything", "they", "can", "to", "give", "their", "child", "as", "loving", "and", "well-adjusted", "childhood", "as", "possible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 609, "question": "But when you look at it that way, from Queen Victoria to this child, how have things changed for the monarchy?", "question_tokens": ["But", "when", "you", "look", "at", "it", "that", "way", ",", "from", "Queen", "Victoria", "to", "this", "child", ",", "how", "have", "things", "changed", "for", "the", "monarchy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "Well, you've had a change of family.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "'ve", "had", "a", "change", "of", "family", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Queen Victoria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "At what age will this little boy understand that he is not like everybody else?", "question_tokens": ["At", "what", "age", "will", "this", "little", "boy", "understand", "that", "he", "is", "not", "like", "everybody", "else", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "MD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "Well, in a way he will be quite like a lot of people.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "in", "a", "way", "he", "will", "be", "quite", "like", "a", "lot", "of", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "JJ", "RB", ",", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 632, "question": "You know, how does that happen?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "how", "does", "that", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 633, "answer": "Well, the -- I know one royal intimately, and what he said was like he just always knew because you know that this particular relation, I mean, he will be introduced to his great grandmother and they will say, this is your great grandmother and you have to bow, you call her mum.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "--", "I", "know", "one", "royal", "intimately", ",", "and", "what", "he", "said", "was", "like", "he", "just", "always", "knew", "because", "you", "know", "that", "this", "particular", "relation", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "he", "will", "be", "introduced", "to", "his", "great", "grandmother", "and", "they", "will", "say", ",", "this", "is", "your", "great", "grandmother", "and", "you", "have", "to", "bow", ",", "you", "call", "her", "mum", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "IN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 643, "question": "No matter what about parliament and we have modern represented democracy there, what is that like to have that on you?", "question_tokens": ["No", "matter", "what", "about", "parliament", "and", "we", "have", "modern", "represented", "democracy", "there", ",", "what", "is", "that", "like", "to", "have", "that", "on", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "WP", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "VBN", "NN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 644, "answer": "Well, I think that's about bringing your kids up right.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "'s", "about", "bringing", "your", "kids", "up", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]